{
	"questions": [
    {
		"key": "99",
		"question": "Pick Your Product",
		"shortname": "Products",
		"optionalContentPage": "",
		"imageVariant": "0",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Pro",
			"link": "98"
		}, {
			"answer": "Central",
			"link": "97"
		}, {
			"answer": "Hamachi",
			"link": "96"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "98",
		"question": "What is your issue?",
		"shortname": "Pro Troubleshooting",
		"optionalContentPage": "",
		"imageVariant": "0",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Remote Printing",
			"link": "0"
		}, {
			"answer": "Other",
			"link": "ContactUs"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "97",
		"question": "What is your issue?",
		"shortname": "Central Troubleshooting",
		"optionalContentPage": "",
		"imageVariant": "0",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Remote Printing",
			"link": "0"
		}, {
			"answer": "Other",
			"link": "ContactUs"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "96",
		"question": "What is your issue?",
		"shortname": "Hamachi Troubleshooting",
		"optionalContentPage": "",
		"imageVariant": "0",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Other",
			"link": "ContactUs"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "0",
		"question": "Does your local printer appear in the Windows Devices and Printers?",
		"shortname": "Check Local Printer",
		"optionalContentPage": "ClientDevicesAndPrinters",
		"imageVariant": "1",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Yes",
			"link": "1"
		}, {
			"answer": "No",
			"link": "FixLocalPrinter"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "1",
		"question": "Does the local printer appear checked off in the remote session printer options?",
		"shortname": "Check Remote Session Options",
		"optionalContentPage": "RemotePrinterOptions",
		"imageVariant": "2",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Yes",
			"link": "3"
		}, {
			"answer": "No, the printer is not checked off",
			"link": "2"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "2",
		"question": "Does the printer appear on the list, but is not checked off?",
		"shortname": "Remote Printer Not Selected",
		"optionalContentPage": "RemotePrinterNotSelected",
		"imageVariant": "3",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Yes",
			"link": "2_1"
		}, {
			"answer": "No",
			"link": "RemotePrinterConnectionIssue"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "3",
		"question": "Does the local printer appear as the via logmein printer by default in Windows Devices and Printers on the Host?",
		"shortname": "Check Devices and Printers on host computer",
		"optionalContentPage": "LogmeinDevicesAndPrinters",
		"imageVariant": "2",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Yes",
			"link": "4"
		}, {
			"answer": "No",
			"link": "NoLogmeinDefaultPrinter"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "4",
		"question": "Can you print a test page from the via LogMeIn printer?",
		"shortname": "Remote Printer Test Page",
		"optionalContentPage": "PrintingTestPage",
		"imageVariant": "1",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Yes",
			"link": "RemotePrintingWorking"
		}, {
			"answer": "No",
			"link": "5"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "5",
		"question": "Is the remote printer connected but you still can't print?",
		"shortname": "Clear Print Queue",
		"optionalContentPage": "",
		"imageVariant": "1",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Yes",
			"link": "ClearPrintQueue"
		}, {
			"answer": "No",
			"link": "6"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "6",
		"question": "Are you encountering a different remote printing issue?",
		"shortname": "Other Issues",
		"optionalContentPage": "Steps",
		"imageVariant": "2",
		"answers": [{
			"answer": "Yes, remote printing options do not appear",
			"link": "FeatureLimitedSession"
		}, {
			"answer": "Yes, remote printing is grayed out",
			"link": "RemotePrintingGrayedOut"
		}, {
			"answer": "No. Other?",
			"link": "ContactUs"
		}]
	}, {
		"key": "FixLocalPrinter",
		"question": "",
		"shortname": "",
		"optionalContentPage": "CheckPlugInkPaperDriver",
		"imageVariant": "2",
		"answers": []
	}, {
		"key": "RemotePrinterConnectionIssue",
		"question": "",
		"shortname": "",
		"optionalContentPage": "NoPopup",
		"imageVariant": "4",
		"answers": []
	}, {
		"key": "NoLogmeinDefaultPrinter",
		"question": "",
		"shortname": "",
		"optionalContentPage": "NoDefault",
		"imageVariant": "4",
		"answers": []
	}, {
		"key": "RemotePrintingWorking",
		"question": "",
		"shortname": "",
		"optionalContentPage": "RemotePrintingWorking",
		"imageVariant": "5",
		"answers": []
	}, {
		"key": "ClearPrintQueue",
		"question": "",
		"shortname": "",
		"optionalContentPage": "ClearPrintQueue",
		"imageVariant": "1",
		"answers": []
	}, {
		"key": "FeatureLimitedSession",
		"question": "",
		"shortname": "",
		"optionalContentPage": "FeatureLimitedSession",
		"imageVariant": "3",
		"answers": []
	}, {
		"key": "RemotePrintingGrayedOut",
		"question": "",
		"shortname": "",
		"optionalContentPage": "AccountIssue",
		"imageVariant": "4",
		"answers": []
	}, {
		"key": "ContactUs",
		"question": "",
		"shortname": "",
		"optionalContentPage": "ContactUs",
		"imageVariant": "4",
		"answers": []
	}, {
		"key": "2_1",
		"question": "Check the printer and select it. If it connects properly, a pop-up will appear at the bottom right corner of the screen indicating that the remote printer connected. Did this work?",
		"shortname": "Remote Printer Not Selected 2",
		"optionalContentPage": "RemotePrinterPopup",
		"imageVariant": "3",
    	"answers": []
	}]
}
